<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    <string id="st_af_nk_doom_name">
        <text>Doom</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_doom_descr">
        <text>
		Rip and tear until it is done. Rumors say that some drunk bandit went on a rampage with just this artifact and his trusty knife against multiple bloodsuckers and survived. The artifact increases protection against all mutant attacks and supports various regenerative processes, further aiding in battle. Prolonged usage is extremely taxing on the user, eventually leading to becoming a mad beast obsessed with fighting and losing your mind. Extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 4 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]High psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]Extremely high rupture protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High impact protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_bloodcompass_name">
        <text>Blood Compass</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_bloodcompass_descr">
        <text>
		A relatively new artifact in the Zone, only a handful of people have seen it. Unlike its brother artifact Compass, it allows you to face danger and your fears instead of avoiding them. When you touch this artifact, your entire body feels like it's on fire. The eerie red glow fills you with courage and you understand that if you can somehow manage its drawbacks, this artifact can substantially aid you in your journeys. Extremely radioactive and expensive, possibly the most prized artifact found in the Zone.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 4 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Strong anti-gravity field
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_archdragonseye_name">
        <text>Archdragon's Eye</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_archdragonseye_descr">
        <text>
		An incredibly strong artifact that can heal most wounds and even radiation poisoning in usually less than a minute. You are afraid to hold it, let alone even look straight into the eye. Its gaze follows your every step, you feel as if it wants to burn you alive. For some reason it's popular among collectors, maybe they like to chase people off with it or want to heal some old wounds? Either way it's very expensive and that makes you a happy stalker, even though you feel like you might run into a burner anomaly if you sell this artifact.
		\n \n%c[0,133,32,12]Tier 4 Coagulative Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]High radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_goldenchrysanthemum_name">
        <text>Golden Chrysanthemum</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_goldenchrysanthemum_descr">
        <text>
		A beautiful flower, it seems to have grown in an anomalous zone over an underground precious metal deposit, resulting in partial replacement of chlorophyll with gold. A digging operation to find the vein would probably be near impossible with all of the anomalies around so you'll have to be content with just this flower. It boasts a very strong anti-gravity field and can also filter out various toxins and radioactive particles from the user. It is very fragile and would melt in high temperatures, alongside with the person wearing it. It also makes the user susceptible to all forms of physical damage and bleeding. Very expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,0]Tier 4 Anti-gravity Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Extremely strong anti-gravity field
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_foolsgold_name">
        <text>Fool's Gold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_foolsgold_descr">
        <text>
		An artifact that looks like a chunk of gold but is actually just severely gravitationally malformed pyrite. Has an extremely strong anti-gravity field that allows you to carry an extra amount of loot, boosts your energy and also increases your reflexes in combat. Comes with many drawbacks but the price is not one of them, possibly one of the most prized artifacts in the Zone.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,0]Tier 4 Anti-gravity Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Extremely strong anti-gravity field
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_galaxy_name">
        <text>Galaxy</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_galaxy_descr">
        <text>
		A spherical artifact of great mass and price. Looks like a galaxy trapped in a glass globe, hence the name. It has amazing radiation filtering capabilities, allowing you to carry multiple artifacts or stay in radioactive environments for longer periods of time. Soothes the mind of nearby beings, increasing psychic protection and lowering aggression of mutants. Continuously drains energy and vitality from the user to upkeep its effects. It's so heavy that you could probably kill someone if you tossed it at someone's head.
		\n \n%c[0,255,217,102]Tier 4 Anti-rad Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Medium risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Minor vitality drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_blackhole_name">
        <text>Black Hole</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_blackhole_descr">
        <text>
		A mini black hole. With a bit of finesse you can push it around and "hold" it while it levitates in your hands. You can't push through the gravity field or touch the center if it even exists, the artifact just slips away and falls to the ground. It sucks up various things to the benefit of the user like radiation, bullets, high temperature and toxic particles, but also absorbs or speeds up other nearby things like lightning, mutant claws or blood coming out of your wounds. Extremely expensive and heavy when equipped.
		\n \n%c[0,255,217,102]Tier 4 Anti-rad Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Medium risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Medium thermal protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Medium chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_dahlia_name">
        <text>Dahlia</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_dahlia_descr">
        <text>
		As beautiful as it is deadly, the delicate Dahlia flower that was turned into an artifact promises many health benefits but will try to kill you in chemical and electric anomaly zones or slowly drive you insane. Very radioactive and expensive, one of the most prized artifacts in the Zone, the price driven up by foolish collectors outside of it. There have been multiple reports of people mysteriously dying after coming in contact with this artifact.
		\n \n%c[0,133,32,12]Tier 4 Coagulative Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Highly radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_everlastinglove_name">
        <text>Everlasting Love</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_everlastinglove_descr">
        <text>
		Fire and water stuck in an anti-gravity field in the shape of a heart, a possible evolution of the Heart artifact but it is unconfirmed. You can't directly touch the artifact, only move the field around. Even if you could you'd just burn yourself. Inhaling the steam seems to have calming and regenerative properties. Severely radioactive and increases vulnerability to fire and electricity, but thanks to the benefits of extra vitality restoration, calmness, carry capacity and the price, you feel like you might fall in love with this artifact.
		\n \n%c[0,213,70,125]Tier 4 Vitality Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Medium anti-gravity field
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_anomalousliver_name">
        <text>Anomalous Liver</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_anomalousliver_descr">
        <text>
		Every time you take a bite you don't feel very good but at least you're not hungry anymore. The liver regenerates extremely fast and never runs out. Judging by the size it might be a remaining piece of a chimera that accidentally ran into a gravity anomaly. Might solve the world's hunger problem if you were to sell it to some Scientist so it's probably worth a lot of money.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 2 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Extremely high psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,0,0]Extremely satiating
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_rubyrose_name">
        <text>Ruby Rose</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_rubyrose_descr">
        <text>
		A ruby gemstone formation loosely resembling the shape of a rose. The sharp crystals have the ability to pierce through your outfit and skin, fueling this artifact's regenerative and protective powers with your own blood. Extremely radioactive and expensive, due to its strong properties and the fact that it is made out of a valuable gem, both stalkers and collectors want one in their collection.
		\n \n%c[0,213,70,125]Tier 4 Vitality Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Extremely high vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_electrolytes_name">
        <text>Electrolytes</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_electrolytes_descr">
        <text>
		A distant cousin of the Mama's Beads artifact. The little blue packets are filled with an electrolyte fluid that increases the user's stamina, reflexes and regenerative capabilities. Vulnerable to evaporating, the artifact will try to steal water and electrolytes from the user's body when exposed to high temperatures. It is also very easy to pierce the sacks, caution is advised when fighting mutants. Extremely radioactive and very expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,0,200,255]Tier 4 Energy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]Medium energy restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_luminewheel_name">
        <text>Lumine Wheel</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_luminewheel_descr">
        <text>
		The artifact was originally first spotted at the Dredge Station in Zaton, it has since then been replicated by the Zone and now copies of it with new properties are showing up here and there. This current specimen has become a very strong energy artifact. It increases the user's stamina and resistance to psy waves. Being made out of an unknown, living metal, it is still vulnerable to corroding and electricity, conducting excess amounts straight at the user. The extreme radioactivity has made this artifact shine very brightly.
		\n \nCan be used to light up the surrounding area in darkness, sometimes used by mutant exterminating forces or stalkers that want to light up enemy positions.
		\n \n%c[0,0,200,255]Tier 4 Energy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,0,0]Emits a lot of light
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]High energy restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_amber_name">
        <text>Amber</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_amber_descr">
        <text>
		Simple amber gem, turned into an artifact in one of the numerous blowouts. Incredibly hot to the touch, it burns away radiation and flesh alike. Can be sold for an alright price.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 1 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Medium chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]High radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_topaz_name">
        <text>Topaz</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_topaz_descr">
        <text>
		A topaz in the rough, it filters a small amount of radiation but attracts extra psy waves. This particular kind of waves interferes with wound healing through unknown mechanisms. Fairly cheap artifact.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 0 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Medium risk of bleeding
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Medium radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_garnet_name">
        <text>Garnet</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_garnet_descr">
        <text>
		A possibly sentient blood red garnet, its anti-rad and anti-psy power is fueled by your own blood and it will do anything to feed on it, like further opening your wounds or creating mini gravity fields that speed up mutant attacks. Fairly expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 2 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Minor vitality drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_tourmarine_name">
        <text>Tourmarine</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_tourmarine_descr">
        <text>
		A tourmarine gem rock formation. Due to anomalous influence it has turned into an artifact. It boasts extremely high radiation filtering and psy protection with some strong drawbacks that shouldn't be too much of a problem for a veteran stalker. Expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 3 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]Medium energy drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ametrine_name">
        <text>Ametrine</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ametrine_descr">
        <text>
		One of the strongest anti-rad artifacts in the Zone, another gem that turned into an artifact thanks to anomalous interference. It can upkeep multiple high tier artifacts and also regenerate a small amount of psy health. The user cannot venture into anomalous zones while wearing this artifact, it would be simply suicide due to the severe protection nullification caused by this artifact's unique psy waves. They also cause some extra hunger through possible rewiring of the hunger signals in the brain. It's also fragile, meaning combat situations risk the artifact breaking and becoming unstable. Scientists speculate that it would result in a mini singularity that sucks the user in but no one has seen this happen yet. The artifact overall is quite the enigma, there is still a lot of things not well understood about it. One thing that is known though is that it is extremely expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,0,0]Tier 4 Unique Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,0,0]Causes medium hunger
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_magmashard_name">
        <text>Magma Shard</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_magmashard_descr">
        <text>
		An incredibly durable magma stone with blazing hot, sharp edges. Most probably a product of thermal anomalies but Scientists argue that it could have come from some deep underground lava shafts. It is not known how deep downwards the Zone extends into the Earth. It can be used as a makeshift melee weapon if skillfully affixed to a fireproof pole, or as an armor plate if you can avoid touching the lava blades. The dark stone absorbs excess heat from the air and transfers it to the edges which continuously burn your skin and can easily pierce it. Handling with the utmost care is advised. Extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \nCan be used to light up the surrounding area in darkness, sometimes used by mutant exterminating forces or stalkers that want to light up enemy positions.
		\n \n%c[0,255,160,0]Tier 4 Thermal Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,0,0]Emits a lot of light
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ash_name">
        <text>Ash</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ash_descr">
        <text>
		A ball of clumped up radioactive ash. A biological scan done by Scientists revealed that this artifact is primarily made out of items and living things that were burnt in thermal anomalies. Absorbs heat and psy waves, converting them into light and toxic particles. Exposing the artifact to extra chemicals can cause it to release stored toxic particles which can subsequently have a disastrous effect on the user's health. Fairly dense and heavy, extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \nCan be used to light up the surrounding area in darkness, sometimes used by mutant exterminating forces or stalkers that want to light up enemy positions.
		\n \n%c[0,255,160,0]Tier 4 Thermal Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,0,0]Emits a lot of light
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_emerald_name">
        <text>Emerald</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_emerald_descr">
        <text>
		An anomalous emerald crystal with incredibly high purity. It filters out various toxins, radiation and stabilizes the user's blood ph, allowing for more controlled breathing and increased stamina. Extremely fragile, the artifact can only endure a small amount of damage before exploding with anomalous energy. Collectors outside of the Zone are very interested in purchasing one of these for their collections. That, in combination with the strong positive properties and simple drawbacks, results in the price being one of the highest of all artifacts.
		\n \n%c[0,200,255,0]Tier 4 Acidic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]Extremely high combat vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]Extremely high physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_stoneskull_name">
        <text>Stone Skull</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_stoneskull_descr">
        <text>
		A fossilized skull covered in various organic matter and moss. Scientists speculate that the artifact weighing down on the user has something to do with a massive amount of gas being produced and trapped in a gravity bubble inside of the artifact when it touches living people, but most stalkers think it's just the soul of the poor guy. The skull releases counter-toxin gas that protects from chemicals, psy waves and also regenerates the user. Metallic formations in the artifact attract extra radiation and electricity. Very expensive, one of the most prized artifacts in the Zone.
		\n \n%c[0,200,255,0]Tier 4 Acidic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Minor gravity field
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high chemical protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_zeus_name">
        <text>Zeus</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_zeus_descr">
        <text>
		A crystallized mass with a glowing orb at the center, named after a Greek God. It seems to hold an endless amount of energy, absorbing all electricity around it and completely protecting from damage. It also absorbs massive amounts of psy and even radio waves from a several kilometer radius, disrupting communications and weakening local mutants' powers at the cost of the user's psyche. Using this artifact for a prolonged amount of time tires the user out and eventually completely overloads the brain and the nervous system, leading to an instant death. Whenever multiple PDAs stop working at the same time, a team of stalkers knows it's time to hunt for a Zeus. Extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \nThe artifact seems to store an endless amount of electrical energy. It converts it and transfers it to the user, drastically increasing combat reflexes.
		\n \n%c[0,74,134,232]Tier 4 Electric Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]Medium energy drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]High psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]Extremely high combat protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_taser_name">
        <text>Taser</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_taser_descr">
        <text>
		A rock formation filled with a mineral called kyanite. After turning into an artifact, it now absorbs electrical energy and stores most of it at the tip, the charge is so strong that it can jump and incapacitate an opponent for a few seconds just like a taser. Useful against mutants that have gotten a bit too close. The electrical shocks due to proximity to the body also periodically affect the user to a smaller degree, damaging but also replenishing energy and stamina. The rock is extremely radioactive, vulnerable to high heat, chemicals and greedy traders.
		\n \nThe artifact stores electrical energy, converts it and transfers it to the user, increasing stamina.
		\n \n%c[0,74,134,232]Tier 4 Electric Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_transistor_name">
        <text>Transistor</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_transistor_descr">
        <text>
		A squiggly piece of the electric network that powers trains. It somehow turned into an artifact and was first found in an anomalous train tunnel by a brave team of stalkers working for the Scientists. Since then various versions of it started showing up around the Zone, usually in areas with train tracks. It controls most psy waves around the user, protecting from harm, but also amplifies any local electrical currents to lethal amounts and pulls them in, resulting in a quick death. It also steals some energy from the user to power itself. Extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \nDecreases the amount of pain you feel and makes you braver.
		\n \n%c[0,125,0,210]Tier 4 Psychic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]Medium energy drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_anomalousmarijuana_name">
        <text>Anomalous Marijuana</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_anomalousmarijuana_descr">
        <text>
		Most probably the only thing left from a Freedomer that stepped into an anomaly. One of his teammates reported that they were trying to grow weed near anomalies to see if it would gain new properties, and they succeeded. After the accident though, he decided that he doesn't want to participate in growing it anymore and destroyed the recipe. The plant turned into an artifact and its edges became purple, it is now growing in some spots in the Zone, randomly being spread by anomalies and getting even more people high. It's so potent that just smelling it has an effect on the endocannabinoid system, protecting from psy waves and also healing the user. The anomalous high makes you very slow in combat though, resulting in extra hits and damage taken. Duty stalkers have been ordered to destroy the plant and stop its growth if it doesn't interfere with their current task, but it seems like a futile effort since The Zone keeps regrowing it in new spots. Highly radioactive but expensive, especially when Freedom is involved.
		\n \n%c[0,125,0,210]Tier 4 Psychic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Highly radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Medium wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_emperor_name">
        <text>Emperor</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_emperor_descr">
        <text>
		A beautiful formation of gold trapped inside of obsidian. Scientists are puzzled over how this was created. Incredibly durable, it can even take a few shots before breaking. You can feel the artifact commanding you various things, increasing your morale, resistance to psy waves, combat awareness and effectiveness. The sharp obsidian easily cuts through anything you put it into, your outfit and the skin, resulting in heavily increased bleeding, making any wound lethal if not treated. Vulnerable to chemicals and extremely radioactive. It is one of the most expensive artifacts in the Zone.
		\n \n%c[0,120,120,120]Tier 4 Combat Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Extremely high chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_titan_name">
        <text>Titan</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_titan_descr">
        <text>
		A rock formation filled with titanium. Extremely durable, it ensures the user's survival in all combat situations by reinforcing skin with the alloy and improving wound regeneration. While the metal itself is fairly resistant, the skin around it is not. It draws in extra heat, electricity and psy waves to the disbenefit of the user. Extremely radioactive and expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,120,120,120]Tier 4 Combat Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]High combat protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_eldenring_name">
        <text>Elden Ring</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_eldenring_descr">
        <text>
		A direct evolution of the Ring artifact. It boasts increased physical and psy protection while also being able to heal most wounds fairly quickly. It absorbs copious amounts of electrical energy from the surroundings and the user, resulting in increased shock damage taken and lower stamina. It is also very easy to melt, high temperatures make the artifact unstable and ignite the artifact, making the user burn alive. Extremely radioactive and expensive but will still yield you no maidens.
		\n \n%c[0,180,225,255]Tier 4 Unyielding Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]Medium energy drain
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Extremely high thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ares_name">
        <text>Ares</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_ares_descr">
        <text>
		Named after the Greek God of war, this spiky artifact increases physical protection and allows you to rapidly heal any wound. Sustained usage without proper equipment is near impossible, not only is the radioactivity extremely high but the artifact itself slowly drives the user insane. It is known that it has something to do with the extremely fast healing process affecting the brain in a negative way but more scientific research is needed to figure out this mechanism completely. Very expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,180,225,255]Tier 4 Unyielding Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High physical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    
<!--
Synthetic Artifacts
-->
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_blackraven_name">
        <text>Black Raven</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_blackraven_descr">
        <text>
		The Scientists' first try at making an artifact out of synthetic materials and various parts of anti-gravity artifacts. Many Ecologists complained about things like not being able to carry a sufficient amount of supplies and equipment out into the field or backpacks being too small for bringing back various samples. The supply of anti-gravity artifacts at the time was low, not everyone was allowed to use them to finish their tasks. The local higher ups had a great idea to confiscate all of them and start experimenting with transmutations and crafting recipes taught by local stalkers. Most of the artifacts were shattered into smaller parts to maximize the amount of artifacts produced, but this caused serious instability in the end product. Codename Black Raven was supposed to aid Ecologists in their tasks by increasing their carry weight, but instead it increased their mortality when going out on already dangerous missions by roughly 200%. The gravity field generated by this artifact does indeed help carry more supplies, but it also increases the speed of any incoming objects and attacks by up to 50 times, always, without a fail resulting in instant death of the user, no matter how small the object or how weak the attack. Colleagues had to be very careful around Ecologists using these artifacts to not accidentally kill their friends by using certain gestures. Jumping and falling down also triggers the unstable gravity field, crushing the legs when landing. The Scientists were unable to remove all radiation from the previous artifacts during transmutation but managed to reduce it by roughly 30%. Extremely expensive and dangerous, deemed cursed among Ecologists and eventually all of these prototypes were returned, now only daredevil stalkers use them to carry more loot.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,255]Synthetic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Highly radioactive
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,120,120,120]Extremely high combat vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]Extremely high physical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Extremely strong anti-gravity field
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_projectd_name">
        <text>Project D</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_projectd_descr">
        <text>
		Wondering how fast a human could run with the help of an artifact, the Scientists attempted creating one that would aid just in that. After a few unfortunate trials that resulted in various wonders like accelerated aging of the user or ultra fast fat cell burning, resulting in quick starvation if the user wasn't chubby enough. The end result, shaped like a triangular pyramid, ended up being named Project D. The original goal of speeding up the user was achieved, the energy restoration properties of the artifact greatly aid in long sprints. After a few experiments and tweaks, the radiation was completely nullified and the drawbacks reduced to simple fatigue from overusage and lack of blood coagulation when using the artifact. Using it in combination with other artifacts is recommended but not necessary. Expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,255]Synthetic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Extremely high risk of bleeding
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic drain
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,255]High energy recovery
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_prototype60_name">
        <text>Prototype 60</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_prototype60_descr">
        <text>
		A heavily modified Moonlight trapped in a specialized container. It has been specifically manufactured just for this artifact to neutralize its radioactivity and further boost its favorable psychic resistance. Prototype 60 is one of the inventions predating the Psi Helmet, it was actually a helmet redesigned into an artifact container, created as an attempt to nullify the effects of the Brain Scorcher in Yantar with the help of artifacts, but it has proven to be too weak and also too expensive and complicated to mass manufacture for Ecologists. The container is vulnerable to various elements. It is now sometimes up for sale at various traders after the Scientists decided to sell off most of their remaining supply. The artifacts were simply taking up too much space with their heavy containers. Expensive.
		\n \nThe custom container does not allow you to use a different one.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,255]Synthetic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]Extremely high shock vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Medium psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_sparklercore_name">
        <text>Sparkler Core</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_sparklercore_descr">
        <text>
		A Sparkler artifact that was dipped in fluoroantimonic acid (don't ask where the Scientists got their hands on that), removing the dangerous outer shell completely and letting the more durable core of the artifact be used to its full potential. All of the negative properties have been removed and the positives have become stronger. Not quite a synthetic artifact but it is impossible to find in the wilderness and is unobtainable without some invasive modifications. Fairly expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,255]Synthetic Artifact
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_stonebloodcore_name">
        <text>Stone Blood Core</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_syn_stonebloodcore_descr">
        <text>
		A Stone Blood artifact that was left over night to cook in a Scientist's artifact oven set to a steady 500 degrees Celcius. The outer radioactive shell was completely burned off, alongside all of the negative aspects. The fireproof core's positive properties have been strengthened and can now be utilized easier. Stalkers have tried replicating this process with burner anomalies but their short bursts of flame are not strong or stable enough for the protective layer to melt. Expensive.
		\n \n%c[0,255,255,255]Synthetic Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,255,0]Minor anti-gravity field
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Minor wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    
<!--
Unstable Artifacts
-->
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_leviathan_name">
        <text>Leviathan</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_leviathan_descr">
        <text>
		One of the first ever failed artifact transmutations and one with the most powerful effects. It came about thanks to a stalker named Nimble. He was experimenting with anti-gravity artifact transmutations, trying to create one that would greatly increase carry weight since that would aid him in the various smuggling trips outside the Zone. After a few failed attempts and nearly dying to a freshly formed gravity anomaly, he succeeded in creating an artifact that was never seen before, with new properties unlike the usual ones. He instinctively grabbed it by the thin middle part, instantly activating it. The artifact's jaws bit his hand, injecting an unknown substance into the bloodstream. Almost fainting due to the toxic effects on the body, he afterwards felt a surge of inhuman energy that let him carry various heavy objects with ease.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-50% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-500 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+50kg carry weight
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_behemoth_name">
        <text>Behemoth</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_behemoth_descr">
        <text>
		A bloody mess, another failed recipe that resulted in an unstable artifact which only bestows temporary bonuses. The Behemoth gives the user inhuman strength which increases stamina levels and grants the ability to carry more of various heavy objects, useful for carrying a lot of loot. The activation procedure involves sacrificing a few drops of blood onto the artifact. After that, it activates a gravity field which makes it lash out at the user with incredible speed, causing physical trauma and some unknown effects in the body during contact.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-30% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-300 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+30kg carry weight
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+180% stamina
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_oasis_name">
        <text>Oasis</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_oasis_descr">
        <text>
		Created by pouring various liquids on the Heart of the Oasis, it soaks all of them up becoming a completely new, unstable artifact, losing all original properties. The water becomes encapsulated within the thick membrane while the branches hold it. The user can then rehydrate with whatever mixture was brewed inside by puncturing it and sipping on what comes out. After a few seconds the membrane heals and closes back up. When emptied though, the artifact shrivels up and dies due to dehydration. A very portable source of water.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-60% thirstiness
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_dungpie_name">
        <text>Dung Pie</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_dungpie_descr">
        <text>
		An unfortunate experiment to some, a source of nutrition to others in tough situations. The Dung Pie is an edible artifact and also an amalgamation of multiple different substances like dirt, wood, artifact shards, mutant crap, unknown fat and proteins with some trace minerals and vitamins. Care to find out how it tastes?
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+600 satiety
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_scarab_name">
        <text>Scarab</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_scarab_descr">
        <text>
		A formation that looks like purple crystallized pincers. Licking the artifact quenches thirst and hunger but also activates its defense mechanisms, hurting the user physically and mentally.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-30% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+300 satiety
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_lancelot_name">
        <text>Lancelot</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_lancelot_descr">
        <text>
		A metallic object created in a transmutation involving artifact parts and a knife. It allows the user to draw blood and alongside it all alcohol content. The process has some minor drawbacks but this artifact allows using various unstable artifacts while completely negating one of their effects, or drinking more alcohol without getting drunk.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-200 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-100% intoxification
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_sunflower_name">
        <text>Sunflower</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_sunflower_descr">
        <text>
		An edible artifact that resembles a sunflower. While slightly toxic, eating a single leaf almost fully rejuvenates the user. Useful in tough situations where using a medkit or a stimpack would simply be too slow for survival. The toxicity does make further fighting difficult though, it is very easy to overdose on the leaves so one has to be careful when eating them.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+80% health
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_bloodclover_name">
        <text>Blood Clover</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_bloodclover_descr">
        <text>
		Instead of chlorophyll, blood runs through these little anomalous clovers. If you can stand the slight toxicity and metallic taste, eating them will replace lost blood very quickly. Easy to overdose, the user has to be careful not to eat too many at once.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+40% health
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_pseudogiantoil_name">
        <text>Pseudogiant Oil</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_pseudogiantoil_descr">
        <text>
		A very concentrated oil obtained from pseudogiant's fat layers under the skin, combined with an artifact in a transmutation process to yield a healing substance. It's an acquired taste, similar to lard yet more liquidy, but the regenerative properties are top notch. It also increases the user's strength momentarily. Quite toxic.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+18% hp/s, total of 180% hp
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+20kg carry weight
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_chimeraoil_name">
        <text>Chimera Oil</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_chimeraoil_descr">
        <text>
		Chimera fat extracted from a freshly hunted specimen. It has undergone a transmutation with an artifact to gain strong healing properties and turn into a liquid. It also increases the user's speed momentarily. Slightly toxic.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+12% hp/s, total of 120% hp
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+180% stamina
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_bloodsuckeroil_name">
        <text>Bloodsucker Oil</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_bloodsuckeroil_descr">
        <text>
		A bottle filled with bloodsucker fat and blood that went through a transmutation process with an artifact to gain new, healing properties. The taste is metallic and the thought of whose blood are you really drinking makes you shiver. Slightly toxic.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+750 wound healing
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+3% hp/s, total of 180% hp
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_sandman_name">
        <text>Sandman</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_sandman_descr">
        <text>
		A small unstable artifact made out of mainly sand, held loosely together by some metallic dust, most probably remains of an anti-gravity artifact. The method of usage is incredibly uncomfortable, it involves breaking off a part of it, grinding it down to dust in your hand and inhaling it to stave off drowsiness. You can guess that inhaling sand and metal isn't very healthy but having an extra 8 hours a day thanks to magical sands seems like a fair tradeoff.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-200 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-100% sleepiness
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_mummy_name">
        <text>Mummy</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_mummy_descr">
        <text>
		2 colorful gemstones intertwined together by a tough, anomalous fiber. Its absorptive properties can be used to manufacture a makeshift bandage by cutting up the artifact. Fairly damp, the fiber is soaked wet with a slightly toxic, sticky fluid that you might not want anywhere near your blood, but the alternative is losing all of it and dying. Upon removing all of the filament, the gemstones turn into liquid and fall to the ground.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+5% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+6000 wound healing
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_anubis_name">
        <text>Anubis</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_anubis_descr">
        <text>
		A small unstable artifact with the power to magnetize all nearby blood, be it your own, your enemies' or old blood on the ground, it brings it through the air back to the user to close any wound. It cannot filter out impurities and toxins that could have gotten into the blood that is being used. The artifact is activated by sticking it to a wound, it then changes its color to blood red and starts sucking in blood, repairing the damage.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+5% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+3000 wound healing
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_hermes_name">
        <text>Hermes</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_hermes_descr">
        <text>
		A butterfly shaped artifact. It is activated by being stomped on by the user's foot, it then creates a small azure colored explosion and slightly injures the legs but also speeds up their metabolism, heavily increasing the user's running capabilities and stamina.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-30% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-300 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+360 stamina
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_acidmushroom_name">
        <text>Acid Mushroom</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_acidmushroom_descr">
        <text>
		A mushroom that was growing in an acid anomaly. It somehow managed to form a symbiotic relationship with the toxic environment, gaining anomalous properties. The user can eat it to gain very high chemical protection at the price of some toxins entering the body and doing some damage initially.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1000% chemical protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_psyshroom_name">
        <text>Psyshroom</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_psyshroom_descr">
        <text>
		A mushroom harvested from dark tunnels filled with either psy fields or electras. Rumors say Controllers eat these to strengthen their powers. The user can consume it to raise their psy defense, at the cost of some toxicity.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1000% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_slimeshroom_name">
        <text>Slimeshroom</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_slimeshroom_descr">
        <text>
		An edible mushroom artifact that's covered with a layer of slime on the top. Upon eating, it strengthens the user's skin against chemical damage and protects the brain from psy waves but also intoxicates the user.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-400 satiety
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+700% chemical protection
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+500% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_midnightamanita_name">
        <text>Midnight Amanita</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_midnightamanita_descr">
        <text>
		A very potent, psychedelic mushroom. Appears in areas of high psy activity, seems to draw power from moonlight. When harvested at midnight, it keeps all of its properties for a very long time without going stale. It can be eaten to completely nullify all psy damage but the best use for it is upkeeping multiple belt artifacts that actively send out harmful psy waves.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1500% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_giantjellyshroom_name">
        <text>Giant Jellyshroom</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_giantjellyshroom_descr">
        <text>
		Anomalous mushroom, usually harvested from flooded areas or swamps with high psy or electra activity. Its cap is transparent and shines brightly. Eating a part of it grants the user extra protection from psy waves but also intoxifies them.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+40% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-400 satiety
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1000% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_lionsagaricus_name">
        <text>Lion's Agaricus</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_lionsagaricus_descr">
        <text>
		A bright yellow anomalous mushroom with red spots. It usually shows up in areas with high gravitational and psy activity. Upon eating, it boosts the user's psy protection but also slightly intoxifies.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-20% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+30% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+500% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_monsoon_name">
        <text>Monsoon</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_monsoon_descr">
        <text>
		Wash away the radiation. Spinning the artifact rapidly will activate it. It then floats in the air for a few seconds, releasing a toxic purple smoke that disrupts the user's various body functions, resulting in internal trauma but also massively increased radiation filtering. 
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-60% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-400 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-420 rads/s, total of 25200 rads
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_cube_name">
        <text>Cube</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_cube_descr">
        <text>
		An unstable artifact made out of cubes that come in various shapes, held together by a gravity field. Activating it involves moving around the pieces in a specific order. Upon activation, the artifact's gravity field pulls radiation to itself and dissipates it. The field itself also has other harmful effects on the body that use mechanisms unknown to science. The initial few seconds of exposure are especially painful.
		\n \nWith every activation the artifact loses gravitational energy and upon the final use it falls apart.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-50% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-200 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+20% intoxification
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-300 rads/s, total of 18000 rads
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_coolingrods_name">
        <text>Cooling Rods</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_coolingrods_descr">
        <text>
		An unstable artifact that looks like a few rods stuck together in a black organic mass. Fairly flexible, the rods can be moved around and upon touching two of them together the artifact activates, instantly stealing body temperature and radiation from the user.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-40% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% intoxification
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-180 rads/s, total of 10800 rads
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_hourglass_name">
        <text>Hourglass</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_hourglass_descr">
        <text>
		An hourglass shaped artifact with a shiny red gem in the middle. It can be activated by trying to pull it out. Every attempt causes the artifact to lash out at the user with anomalous energy while making sounds resembling an owl. The effect causes some bleeding but also short term radiation filtering.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-30% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% intoxification
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-120 rads/s, total of 7200 rads
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_dawn_name">
        <text>Dawn</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_dawn_descr">
        <text>
		Two pyramid shaped objects glued together by a strong gravity field. Pulling them apart requires some strength and can only be done for a few seconds. Doing so destabilizes the unusual gravity field, quickly pulling the pyramids together which results in a lot of sharp artifact fragments flying off everywhere, harming the user, but also granting several benefits for a few minutes.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-40% health
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+5kg carry weight
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-60 rads/s, total of 10800 rads
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+180% stamina
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_rustyfeather_name">
        <text>Rusty Feather</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_rustyfeather_descr">
        <text>
		A feather from an unknown bird, it has fallen into an anomalous zone, turned partially metallic and started rusting away. The user can crush up a part of the feather and inhale the toxic dust to harness its anomalous power. The rust evaporates a substantial amount of body fluids, removing all radiation but also disrupting most life functions.
		\n \nWith every activation parts of the artifact break off and eventually it crumbles to dust.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]100% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]50% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]20% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-1500 rads/s, total of 45000 rads
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_phoenix_name">
        <text>Phoenix</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_phoenix_descr">
        <text>
		A feather with fiery colors, almost as if it was plucked from a phoenix. Activation process involves burning a part of it with a fire source and inhaling the smoke. It's so potent that it puts the user to sleep almost instantly. After sleeping you will feel almost completely rejuvenated.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+100% sleepiness, wake up with a minor amount of thirstiness and sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-3000 radiation
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+100% health
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1000 satiety
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-100% intoxification
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_gluttony_name">
        <text>Gluttony</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_gluttony_descr">
        <text>
		A star shaped artifact. Method of use involves removing one of its 8 arms. The central sphere crumbles to dust when all of them have been used. When an arm is broken off, the artifact instantly generates a massive amount of new red blood cells in the user, enough to heal all wounds and damage, while eating up a massive amount of food and water. The process is so fast that the sudden shock the body goes through can make you pass out due to dehydration.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-500 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+50% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+100% health
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_snakeoil_name">
        <text>Snake Oil</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_snakeoil_descr">
        <text>
		An extremely potent and toxic oil, the seller assures you it is made out of snakes caught in the Zone. It's probably an unknown substance that has undergone an artifact transmutation. The oil at first almost kills the user but very rapidly regenerates all of the damage caused and continues to heal for some extra time.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-85% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+10% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+60% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+24% hp/s, total of 480% hp
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_devilsheavendeath_name">
        <text>Devil's Heavendeath</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_un_devilsheavendeath_descr">
        <text>
		An incredibly toxic mushroom, named appropriately for how dangerous it is and how it makes you feel. Stalkers that have consumed one and passed out never woke up again. If you manage to survive eating a part of it and get your mind and body back in shape, it actually does grant a lot of benefits. Only for the bravest, the stupidest or the most suicidal Stalkers.
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Unstable Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,125]Upon use:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-98% health
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]-600 satiety
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+100% intoxification
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+60% thirstiness
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,0,0]+60% sleepiness
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+20kg carry weight
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]-60 rads/s, total of 39960 rads
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+1.5% hp/s, total of 999% hp
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+180% stamina
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,0,200,0]+500% psy protection
		\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    
<!--
Legacy Artifacts
-->
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_slime_name">
        <text>Slime</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_slime_descr">
        <text>
		It is certain that this artifact is created by the anomaly called "Fruit Punch". When carried on the belt, the wounds bleed less, although the body of its owner becomes vulnerable to various burns.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 1 Legacy Artifact
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_slug_name">
        <text>Slug</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_slug_descr">
        <text>
		Formed by the "Fruit Punch" anomaly. The negative qualities of this artifact are compensated by the fact that it heightens the coagulation quality of blood. It's not often that one runs into such an artifact, and they pay well for it too.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 2 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]Medium thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]Medium chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]Medium wound healing
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mica_name">
        <text>Mica</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mica_descr">
        <text>
		Anomaly "Fruit Punch" is able to create such an artifact at the rarest, most extreme collection of physical conditions. The result is a semi-transparent, hard object. A rare and expensive artifact.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal vulnerability
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical vulnerability
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,133,32,12]High wound healing
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_stoneblood_name">
        <text>Stone Blood</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_stoneblood_descr">
        <text>
		You can find this artifact near the anomaly "Whirligig". It is quite an ugly reddish object made out of pressed together and curiously bent polymerized remnants of plants, soil, and bones. Quite widespread and not very effective.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 1 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Minor vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_meatchunk_name">
        <text>Meat Chunk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_meatchunk_descr">
        <text>
		Manufactured by the Whirligig anomaly. Causes increased cell growth. On the other hand, the newly formed cells are much more receptive to the effects of physical uranium. The artifact doesn't show up very often, but it's hard to call it rare.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 2 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]Medium vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_soul_name">
        <text>Soul</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_soul_descr">
        <text>
		Very rarely found artifact, located near the Whirligig anomaly. Only a very few manage to find this artifact, and few have even seen it. It has a nice shape and an equally nice price.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,213,70,125]High vitality restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_droplets_name">
        <text>Droplets</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_droplets_descr">
        <text>
		Formed in the anomaly "Burner" at high temperatures. From the exterior looks like a tear-like shade compound with a glossy surface, covered in cracks.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 1 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Medium radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_stoneflower_name">
        <text>Stone Flower</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_stoneflower_descr">
        <text>
		Born in the Springboard anomaly. This artifact is found in only a few areas of the Zone. The bits of metallic compounds create a beautiful light play. It is very calming to study this artifact at night by the fire.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 2 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Moderately radioactive
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_nightstar_name">
        <text>Night Star</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_nightstar_descr">
        <text>
		This wonderful artifact is formed by the Springboard anomaly. The use of the artifact demands the neutralization of deadly radiation. Expensive and rare, this artifact is extremely interesting for scientific expeditions and other research activity in the Zone.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Highly radioactive
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_thorn_name">
        <text>Thorn</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_thorn_descr">
        <text>
		The result of the interaction between the anomaly Burnt Fuzz and the body of a careless stalker. The Thorn artifact pokes the body of its owner, no matter what. But it also helps clean the body of radionucliodes. Quite widespread and cheap.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 1 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Medium radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_crystalthorn_name">
        <text>Crystal Thorn</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_crystalthorn_descr">
        <text>
		Crystallizes in the anomaly Burnt Fuzz. Naturally takes out the radiation from the organism. That is, through the ears along with some amount of blood. Blood loss is possible also through other openings. Widespread and quite effective, which is the cause for the stable price in the artifact market.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 2 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]High radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_urchin_name">
        <text>Urchin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_urchin_descr">
        <text>
		The anomaly Burnt Fuzz very rarely gives rise to this artifact. Blood pressure rises, the body gets rid of a large amount of red blood cells. But along with them the stored radiation leaves the body as well. In his fundamental work titled "Ionization and polarization of the components of rare artifacts", Sakharov noted that the content of this formation has a critical stability, and it's not realistic to create such an artifact in lab conditions in the next ten years.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Extremely high radiation filtering
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_wrenched_name">
        <text>Wrenched</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_wrenched_descr">
        <text>
		Located in the anomaly called "Vortex". When it touches the body it disseminates the direction of the radiation, protecting from scratches or wounds made by mutants. This artifact isn't hard to find, that's why they don't pay much for it.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 1 Legacy Artifact
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_gravi_name">
        <text>Gravi</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_gravi_descr">
        <text>
		Can spot it near anomalies such as "Vortex" or in the hands of another stalker. While wearing it, a certain amount of radiation is stored in the body while the rest of it is scattered in the radial direction away from the body. A good price.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 2 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Moderately radioactive
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_goldfish_name">
        <text>Goldfish</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_goldfish_descr">
        <text>
		An artifact formed in the Vortex anomaly. It is activated by the heat of the body. Decide what's worse: radiation or mutant wounds, and choose the lesser of the two evils. In any case you can sell the artifact for good profit.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,150,0,0]Disadvantages:
		\n%c[0,150,0,0] • %c[0,255,217,102]Highly radioactive
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_kolobok_name">
        <text>Kolobok</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_kolobok_descr">
        <text>
		When you hold this mystery of the Zone in your hands, you feel how your skin becomes tougher and less sensitive. You can still shoot through it with a bullet, but it's much more difficult to cut through
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_shell_name">
        <text>Shell</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_shell_descr">
        <text>
		When wearing this artifact the denaturalization of proteins happens slower. In other words, the flesh is able to endure higher temperatures and burns less. In itself it is an expensive and rare thing.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,255,160,0]High thermal protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_pellicle_name">
        <text>Pellicle</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_pellicle_descr">
        <text>
		This artifact is so rare that many researchers can't even imagine that such a substance can exist in a natural setting. Emits acidic chemical components.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,200,255,0]High chemical protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_battery_name">
        <text>Battery</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_battery_descr">
        <text>
		The origin of this object is shrouded in scientific mystery. It's clear that it's made in part by di-electric elements, but science does not know the physical conditions in which it is formed.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,74,134,232]High shock protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_spring_name">
        <text>Spring</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_spring_descr">
        <text>
		According to the opinion of some researchers-theorists, this artifact is a hybrid between Battery and Shell.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,180,225,255]High impact protection
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mercuryball_name">
        <text>Mercury Ball</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mercuryball_descr">
        <text>
		Resembling a large fluorescent ball overgrown with moss, the artifact's properties are not well understood. What is known though is that it does provide some protection from harmful psy-waves.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n \n%c[0,0,150,0]Advantages:
		\n%c[0,0,150,0] • %c[0,125,0,210]Minor psychic restoration
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mamasbeads_name">
        <text>Mama's Beads</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_nk_leg_mamasbeads_descr">
        <text>
		An extremely rare artifact. Keep it safe because it has no negative qualities. Scientists cannot figure out how to create such an object in laboratories.
		\n \n%c[0,200,100,50]Tier 3 Legacy Artifact
		\n
		</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
