<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_operator">
        <text>Rifle Kit "Operator" (LEWD)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_operator_descr">
        <text>
This tacticool weapon kit will upgrade a base weapon (rifle size) with performance parts and scopes, enhancing it's battle readiness for special operations.
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_specialist">
        <text>Rifle Kit "Specialist" (LEWD)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_specialist_descr">
        <text>
This specialized weapon kit will upgrade a base weapon with selected parts and scopes, to perform with excellence in a specialist role, such as an infiltrator.
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_marksman">
        <text>Rifle Kit "marksman" (LEWD)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_marksman_descr">
        <text>
This precision weapon kit will upgrade a base weapon with fine-tuned parts and scopes, to significantly raise its long-range engagement and sniper capabilites.
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_warmonger">
        <text>Rifle Kit "Warmonger" (LEWD)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_lewd_warmonger_descr">
        <text>
This brutal weapon kit will upgrade a base weapon with hardened parts and scopes, to enhance sustained high-RPM fire and maximize the kill-ratio in close quarter.
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_g33_flipup">
        <text>Scope kit Aimpoint PRO and EOTech G33 (flipped up)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_g33_flipup_descr">
        <text>
This scope kit mounts a combined Aimpoint PRO reddot sight with an EOTech G33 magnifier scope (switched up) to the rifle. If it's already mounted with the G33 switched to the side, then this kit can be used to flip the G33 up.
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_g33_flipdown">
        <text>Scope kit Aimpoint PRO and EOTech G33 (flipped down)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_kit_g33_flipdown_descr">
        <text>
This scope kit mounts a combined Aimpoint PRO reddot sight with an EOTech G33 magnifier scope (switched to the side) to the rifle. If it's already mounted with the G33 flipped up, then this kit can be used to switch the G33 to the side.
		</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
