<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic">
		<text>Colt M1911 "Classic"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic_s">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic_descr">
		<text>This is the original Colt 1911, made by John Moses Browning in 1910 and patented the next year, hence the 1911 designation. Coming to service in 1913, this is considered to be the very first self-loading handgun that is vastly successful, being able to use the .45 ACP and shoot at least 1000 rounds flawlessly. You can tell it's a classic 1911 and not an 1911A1 by the fact it has a smaller ejection port, longer trigger and especially the diamond-shaped grip, also its only magazine of 7, keep it with you. Thanks to the black market going on in The Zone, this true classic has been acquired, though it might have been modified a bit, good luck figuring that out. If you want accuracy using a strong caliber without too much recoil, this might be for you, but it's best used as a backup gun if anything, since it has no way to have a suppressor.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1911\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911a1">
		<text>Colt M1911A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911a1_descr">
		<text>An improvement of the 1911 issued after the criticism from World War I Military in 1924. One major issues including the guard being too small, a less-than ergonomic safety grip, and a bulky trigger requiring heavy force to fire. You simply can't go wrong with this pistol, though some still prefer the original 1911 and find their own ways to avoid the flaws, such as gripping it one-handed to avoid "hammer bites".\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1924\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_tokarev">
		<text>Russian Contract Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_tokarev_descr">
		<text>A "Russian version" of the 1911. This is an old variant where with no Cyrillic stamp indicating it's the version ordered from USA to Russia. It's identical to the American-made 1911, but one key difference is the magazine and barrel are slightly modified allowing any technician to change the caliber from .45 ACP to 7.62x25mm Tokarev.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States, Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1911\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_add_colttokarev_name">
		<text>Change of calibre to 7.62x25</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_add_colt695_name">
		<text>Change of calibre to 9x19</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sw645">
		<text>Smith &amp; Wesson 645</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sw645_descr">
		<text>The Smith &amp; Wesson Model 645 is a .45 ACP compact pistol manufactured in 1985 and discontinued in 1988. Despite so, a lot of folks from the black market are able to obtain them. The S&amp;W 645 is constructed almost entirely from stainless steel and is thus extremely resistant to harsh weather conditions. Since it's very easy to do so, any technician can change the caliber to 9x19, turning it into a S&amp;W Model 659. Overall, a good backup pistol.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Smith &amp; Wesson\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1985\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m45">
		<text>Colt M45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m45_descr">
		<text>A modern variant of the M1911, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. This idea of a better 1911 came in the late 1980s, from the USMC Colonel, Robert Young. It is pretty much an M1911A1 assembled by many manufacturers, since it has the slide from Springfield Armory, Mag Extract and Release from Wilson Combat and everything else from Nowlin Manufacturing. The results, while sounding like a "Frankenstein Monster" of a description, actually does make a pretty pistol that is better than the 1911. The Mercenaries favour it for the fact it's heavily customizable.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1985\n

		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m45a1">
		<text>Colt M45A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m45a1_descr">
		<text>A modern variant of the M1911 and an improvement of the M45, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. Compared to the M45, the M45A1 has a dual recoil spring system that spreads out the recoil force of the .45 ACP round by lowering the peak force of the recoil pulse. Also included is a 3-dot red tritium night sight, a 5-inch national match barrel, ambidextrous safety, picatinny rail for the frame and a desert tan Cerakote finish.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]2012\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svi">
		<text>Strayer Voigt Infinity</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svi_s">
		<text>SVI 2011</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svi_descr">
		<text>Strayer-Voigt Inc. is a manufacturer of M1911-styled modular pistols. The SVI is a pistol marketed for competition so it is rather expensive and rare as it is not available for any army or average arms-bearing citizen. The pistol itself has the massive benefit of having its own trademark Strayer-Voigt magazine holding 15 rounds. It also has been modified in-house to shoot in 3 round burst and includes a blue tritium optic fiber. However, don't expect the same great reliability of the classic 1911.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Strayer Voigt Inc\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]2011\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357">
		<text>Coonan .357 Magnum Compact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357_s">
		<text>Coonan .357</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357_descr">
		<text>The Coonan .357 Magnum is a peculiar semi-auto pistol that uses .357 Magnum through the chassis of a Colt 1911. This is done by changing the barrel, slide, handle and magazine to accommodate the caliber change. Sadly, the weapon isn't exactly the best when it comes to accuracy, but the recoil is tolerable as long as you don't rapid-fire and the handling is great. One main benefit of using this instead of some other .357 pistols like the Desert Eagle is the weight, conceal carry and better Close Quarters Combat.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Origin: %c[ui_gray_1]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Manufacturer:  %c[ui_gray_1]Coonan\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255]Production Year: %c[ui_gray_1]1986\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
