<?xml version='1.0' encoding='WINDOWS-1251'?>
<string_table>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_eotech_g33">
        <text>
            EOTECH Magnifier G33 (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_eotech_g33_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n The G33 Magnifier is the selected magnifier of USSOCOM, and is compact and
            lightweight. The mount provides fast transitioning from 3X to 1X, and the optic
            offers tool-free vertical and horizontal adjustments, larger field-of-view and an
            adjustable diopter for improved, precise focusing.
          \n
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]1.0x - 3.0x
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_razor_amg">
        <text>
            Razor AMG UH-1 (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_razor_amg_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n The Razor AMG UH-1 is fast, intuitive and technologically advanced for close-
            quarters and lightning-fast engagement. A revolutionary type of holographic system
            gives you the impressive sight picture and distortion-free image of a holographic
            sight, with the energy efficiency and durability of a traditional red dot. With an
            ultra-clean sight picture and the incredibly fast EBR-CQB reticle, the UH-1 is sure
            to uncover a level of speed and accuracy in close-quarters you never knew existed.
          \n
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]none
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_hamr">
        <text>
            Leupold Mark 4 HAMR (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_hamr_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n "Tough" doesn't begin to describe the Leupold Mark 4 HAMR, a scope that is as
            devastatingly effective as ruggedly constructed. Compact and combat-ready, the HAMR
            (High Accuracy Multi-Range Riflescope) is designed for precise mid-range distance
            marksmanship and fast target acquisition in bright daylight, low light, and at night.
            The HAMR will give you the upper hand in any Close Quarter and Mid-Range tactical
            scenario. The HAMR comes coupled with a 7.5 MOA DeltaPoint red dot sight for
            immediate target acquisition when needed.
          \n
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]none
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_sig_bravo4">
        <text>
            SIG Bravo4 4x30mm (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_sig_bravo4_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n SIG Bravo4 4x30 - delivers an industry leading 42% wider field of view than
            current battle sights. The notably flat, distortion-free image boasts an
            unprecedented edge-to-edge clarity by means of a combination of Low Dispersion glass
            and aspherical lens design.
          \n
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]fixed 4.0x
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_pinty">
        <text>
            Pinty 3-9x32EB Rifle Scope (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_pinty_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n Magnifications from 3x to 9x, green/red illumination with 5 brightness settings,
            both for the scope and electronic unlimited brightness control for the dot sight.
            Red-green dot reflex sight with unlimited eye coverage and wide field of view.
          \n The Picatinny mount easily mounts to any 22mm rail; Multi-coated optics with
            O-ring sealing and nitrogen filling ensure 100% water and fog proof. Unmatched light
            transmission, uncompromising mechanical performance and clarity - exactly what you
            need in the Zone.
          \n
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]3.0x - 9.0x
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Pre-installed: a range finder scope, a green laser
            sight and a red and green dot sight %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition:
            %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_lco">
        <text>
            Leupold Carbine Optic - LCO (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_lco_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n An open field of view keeps the peripheral vision free of knobs, dials, or the
            scope housing, which can mask targets. The LCO's crisp 1-MOA dot stands out in
            blinding sun or heavy rain, and quickly adjust between its 16 brightness settings to
            match any condition. The LCO is waterproof to 66 feet and can take a beating thanks
            to its aircraft-grade aluminum housing.
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]none
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_d-evo">
        <text>
            Leupold D-EVO 6X20 CMR-W (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_d-evo_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n The D-EVO's unique design allows for a quick move between a 1x red dot sight and
            the 6x magnification D-EVO by simply shifting the eye line – not the head. This
            enables to quickly move between close-quarter shots and mid-range shots with speed
            and accuracy.
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]6.0x
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Pre-installed: a 1x red dot sight %c[d_purple] •
            %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]very good
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_burris-ar332">
        <text>
            Burris AR-332 (LEWD)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_burris-ar332_descr">
        <text>
            
          \n The AR-332 is designed and rugged for harsh environments and changing weather
            conditions. The Ballistic CQ reticle features holdover dots good out to 600 yards.
            They work best with 5.56 or 7.62 ammunition. Picatinny rails allow piggybacking of
            additional sights, lasers or lights. The perfect AR Scope for quick target
            acquistion, coupled with a bit more range.
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_1]3.0x
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Pre-installed: a 1x red dot sight %c[d_purple] •
            %c[ui_gray_2] Condition: %c[ui_gray_1]excellent
        </text>
    </string>
</string_table>
