<?xml version='1.0' encoding='WINDOWS-1251'?>
<string_table>
    <string id="st_wpn_aps_cw">
        <text>
            APS - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_aps_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The Stechkin or APS (Avtomaticheskiy Pistolet Stechkina) is a Soviet selective fire
            machine pistol chambered in 9×18mm Makarov and 9×19mm Parabellum introduced into
            service in 1951 for use with artillery and mortar crews, tank crews and aircraft
            personnel, where a cumbersome assault rifle was deemed unnecessary. Seeing service in
            a number of wars such as the Vietnam War, Russo-Ukrainian War and Syrian Civil War.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] APS Silencer
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_cw">
        <text>
            Beretta 92fs - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The 92FS is a double/single-action semiauto pistol that employs an open-slide, short-
            recoil delayed locking-block system, which yields a faster cycle time and delivers
            exceptional accuracy and reliability. In particular, the open-slide design
            practically eliminates stove-piping and helps flawless cycling and feeding even after
            thousands and thousands of rounds.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm Silencer.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_cw_alt">
        <text>
            Beretta 92fs Tactical - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_beretta_cw_enforcer">
        <text>
            Beretta 92fs 'Enforcer' - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_1911_cw">
        <text>
            Colt 1911 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_1911_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The M1911 (Colt 1911 or Colt Government) is a single-action, recoil-operated, semi-
            automatic pistol chambered for the .45 ACP cartridge.The pistol's formal U.S.
            military designation as of 1940 was Automatic Pistol, Caliber .45, M1911 for the
            original model adopted in March 1911, and Automatic Pistol, Caliber .45, M1911A1 for
            the improved M1911A1 model which entered service in 1926. The designation changed to
            Pistol, Caliber .45, Automatic, M1911A1 in the Vietnam War era.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] .45 Silencer.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_1911_cw_custom">
        <text>
            Colt 1911 'Custom 'Operator' - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_1911_cw_modern">
        <text>
            Colt 1911 Modern - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_1911_cw_new">
        <text>
            Colt 1911 Long Barrel - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_cw">
        <text>
            CZ-75 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_cw_auto">
        <text>
            CZ-75 Auto - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The CZ-75 is a semi-automatic pistol made by Czech firearm manufacturer CZUB. First
            introduced in 1975, it is one of the original "wonder nines" and features a
            staggered-column magazine, all-steel construction, and a hammer forged barrel. It is
            widely distributed throughout the world and is the most common handgun in the Czech
            Republic.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] .45 Silencer.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw">
        <text>
            Desert Eagle - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw_custom">
        <text>
            Desert Eagle Custom - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw_modern">
        <text>
            Desert Eagle Modern - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw_nimble">
        <text>
            Desert Eagle "Bald Eagle" - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The IMI Desert Eagle is a semi-automatic handgun notable for chambering the largest
            centrefire cartridge of any magazine fed, self-loading pistol and also being the
            heaviest and blockiest gun of its type. No one knows why IMI thought shooting a
            calibre of this size out of a handgun was a good idea, even though there are plenty
            of rounds out there that can do the job without breaking your wrist; this one assumes
            because of a pissing contest between the .44 and .50 AE. Not only is it heavy and
            harsh in recoil, you can also use it to bludgeon your enemies to death because of its
            blockiness and weight. Although militaries and law enforcement around the world, in
            their moment of sanity, never adopted this brick; Hollywood did, mostly because of
            its "cool factor" and now is the poster child for gangsters and pimps and a status
            symbol for those who reached a certain rank in a certain console shooter. Rumour is
            that there's a stalker with a crowbar wandering around the Zone with a rechambered
            version of this gun, but it's just a rumour.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_deagle_cw_nimble_descr">
        <text>
            The IMI Desert Eagle is a semi-automatic handgun notable for chambering the largest
            centrefire cartridge of any magazine fed, self-loading pistol and also being the
            heaviest and blockiest gun of its type. No one knows why IMI thought shooting a
            calibre of this size out of a handgun was a good idea, even though there are plenty
            of rounds out there that can do the job without breaking your wrist; this one assumes
            because of a pissing contest between the .44 and .50 AE. This weapon was brought to
            the Zone by a stalker named Logan Williams. Disguised as a TIME photographer he
            managed to single-handedly enter the centre of Pripyat. His current whereabouts are
            unknown, but he is rumoured to work as an information broker specializing in all
            matters related to the Zone.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DOCTER sight (integrated)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fn57_cw">
        <text>
            FN-57 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fn57_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The original FN Five-seveN, often imitated but hardly duplicated, has two decades of
            trusted service with allied armies, global law enforcement and civilians. Extending
            its groundbreaking design is a new, all flat dark earth frame and slide. With
            improved range and accuracy over common pistol cartridges, the NATO standardized
            5.7x28mm developed by FN Herstal is fired from the chrome-lined cold hammer-forged
            barrel. Pinpoint accuracy and minimal felt recoil is standard issue. Equipped with an
            internal hammer, the smooth trigger with a predictable break further enhances
            accuracy. Four new models include all black, and all FDE, with 10-rd or 20-rd
            magazines included. Two existing California-compliant Five-seveN models with 10-rd
            magazines remain unchanged.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7 Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp45_cw">
        <text>
            FNP-45 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp45_custom_cw">
        <text>
            FNP-45 Custom - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp45_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The FN FNP pistol is a series of semi-automatic, polymer-framed pistols manufactured
            in Columbia, South Carolina, by FNH USA, a division of Fabrique Nationale de Herstal.
            The handgun debuted in early 2006 and is variously chambered for the 9×19mm, .40
            S&amp;W, .357 SIG and .45 ACP cartridges. According to FNH USA, the FNP line of pistols
            is the only polymer-framed autoloading pistol on the market (as of its introduction)
            with fully replaceable frame rails; this allows the pistol to be rebuilt after
            extensive firing, thereby extending service life. (Steyr M Series pistols also have
            this feature, and were released in 1999.)
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_cw">
        <text>
            FNX-45 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_cw_alt">
        <text>
            FNX-45 Alternate - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_cw_custom">
        <text>
            FNX-45 Custom - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnx45_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The FN FNX pistol is a series of semi-automatic, polymer-framed pistols manufactured
            in Columbia, South Carolina, by FN America (branded FNH USA), a division of Fabrique
            Nationale d'Herstal. The pistol is chambered for the 9×19mm Parabellum, .40 S&amp;W, and
            .45 ACP cartridges. It was introduced in 2009 as the successor to the FN FNP. All
            variations of the pistols (save some law enforcement models that are decock only)
            include ambidextrous safety/decocking levers, magazine releases, and slide stop
            release levers. All variations also include a Picatinny rail, tritium night sights,
            and a loaded chamber indicator on the right side. New models are sold in a plastic
            hard case with three magazines, and two interchangeable backstraps.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_cw">
        <text>
            Glock 17 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_cw_custom">
        <text>
            Glock-18 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_cw_modern">
        <text>
            Glock-19 Modern - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock_cw_descr">
        <text>
            he Glock 17 is a polymer-frame, short recoil-operated, locked-breech semi-automatic
            pistol chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. It the first pistol in a massive lineup of
            polymer handguns produced by Glock Ges.m.b.H. in Deutsch-Wagram, Austria. The
            manufacturer refers to them as the Glock "Safe Action" Pistol. The company's founder,
            head engineer Gaston Glock, had no experience with firearms design or manufacture at
            the time their first pistol was being prototyped. Glock did, however, have extensive
            experience in advanced synthetic polymers, which was instrumental in the company's
            design of the first commercially successful line of polymer frame handguns.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp443_cw">
        <text>
            MP-443 Grach - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp443_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The MP-443 Grach (" Pistolet Yarygina " ("Yarygin Pistol"), following traditional
            Russian naming procedure, is the Russian standard military-issue side arm .The
            development was headed by the designer Vladimir Alexandrovich Yarygin . It was
            developed under designation " Grach " in response to Russian military trials, which
            began in 1993. In 2003, it was adopted as a standard sidearm for all branches of
            Russian military and law enforcement , alongside the Makarov PM , GSh-18 , and SPS .
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_gsh18_cw">
        <text>
            GSH-18 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_gsh18_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The GSH-18 is a 9 mm semi-automatic pistol developed by the KBP Instrument Design
            Bureau in Tula during the 1990s. The pistol's name is derived from its
            designers—Gryazev and Shipunov—and its magazine capacity of 18 rounds. The GSh-18
            is a rotating-barrel, short recoil , locked-breech pistol with 10 locking lugs spaced
            equally around the barrel, the large locking surface area resulting in a strong
            lockup, making it suitable for high-velocity ammunition loads. The GSh-18 may be
            employed using standard 9×19mm Parabellum rounds, but was designed for the high
            velocity, Russian armour-piercing 9×19mm 7N31 round. The pistol incorporates a pre-
            set striker. The slide and working parts are steel, and the weapon has a polymer
            frame.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_oc33_cw">
        <text>
            OTs-33 'Pernach' - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_oc33_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The OTs-33 Pernach is a Russian 9x18 Makarov machine pistol, derived from the 5.45 mm
            OTs-23 Drotik machine pistol. The Pernach is an automatic pistol designed to replace
            the Stechkin APS in various special OMON units within the Russian police, the Russian
            Ministry of Internal Affairs (MVD) and other paramilitary units. The OTs-33 was
            developed in 1995 by Igor Stechkin at the TsKIB SOO design bureau, and it went into
            limited production at the KBP Instrument Design Bureau. It is also known as the
            SBZ-2, derived from the names of the KBP team responsible for the pistol, namely
            Stechkin, Baltser and Zinchenko.The designers were tasked with resolving the
            difficulty of controlling recoil in full-auto mode present in the Stechkin APS pistol
            and simplifying it for combat deployment. The new pistol has a "square" shape, which
            is simpler (and less expensive) to manufacture and has a novel operating principle
            that increases controllability and reduces recoil.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_cw">
        <text>
            Sig Sauer 220 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_cw_custom">
        <text>
            Sig Sauer 220 Custom - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_cw_nimble">
        <text>
            Sig Sauer 220 "Landfill" - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_sig220_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The SIG Sauer P220 is a semi-automatic pistol. Designed in 1975 by the SIG Arms AG
            division of Schweizerische Industrie Gesellschaft (now SIG Holding AG), and produced
            by J. P. Sauer &amp; Sohn, in Eckernforde; it is currently manufactured by both SIG Sauer
            companies: SIG Sauer GMBH, of Eckernforde, Germany; and SIG Sauer, Inc., of New
            Hampshire, United States. The P220 was developed in 1975 by SIG and produced and
            distributed by J.P. Sauer &amp; Sohn. A new locking system which is known as the SIG
            Sauer system was introduced as well as a number of other innovations. This
            nomenclature is found on the Browning BDA version of the P220 sold from 1975.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] .45 Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_tt33_cw">
        <text>
            TT-33 Tokarev - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_tt333_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The TT-30, commonly known simply as the Tokarev, is an out-of-production Soviet semi-
            automatic pistol. It was developed in 1930 by Fedor Tokarev as a service pistol for
            the Soviet military to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver that had been in use since
            the Russian Empire, though it ended up being used in conjunction with, rather than
            replacing, the M1895. It served until 1952, when it was replaced by the Makarov
            pistol. Externally, the TT-33 is very similar to John Browning's blowback operated FN
            Model 1903 semiautomatic pistol, and internally it uses Browning's short recoil
            tilting-barrel system from the M1911 pistol. In other areas the TT-33 differs more
            from Browning designs—it employs a much simpler hammer/sear assembly than the
            M1911.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] APS Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_cw">
        <text>
            PM Makarov - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_cw_actor">
        <text>
            PM Makarov 'Drum Mag' - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pmm_cw">
        <text>
            PMM Makarov - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_pm_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The Makarov pistol or PM (Pistolet Makarova, lit. 'Makarov's Pistol') is a Soviet
            semi-automatic pistol. Under the project leadership of Nikolay Fyodorovich Makarov,
            it became the Soviet Union's standard military and Militsiya side arm in 1951. The PM
            is a medium-size, straight-blowback-action, all-steel construction, frame-fixed
            barrel handgun. In blowback designs, the only force holding the slide closed is that
            of the recoil spring; upon firing, the barrel and slide do not have to unlock, as do
            locked-breech-design pistols. Blowback designs are simple and more accurate than
            designs using a recoiling, tilting, or articulated barrel, but they are limited
            practically by the weight of the slide.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw">
        <text>
            USP-45 - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw_custom">
        <text>
            USP-45 Custom - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw_match">
        <text>
            USP Match - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw_nimble">
        <text>
            USP Match "Protest" - Freedom
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw_descr">
        <text>
            The USP (Universelle Selbstladepistole or "universal self-loading pistol") is a semi-
            automatic pistol developed in Germany by Heckler &amp; Koch GmbH (H&amp;K) as a replacement
            for the P7 series of handguns. The USP is a semi-automatic pistol with a mechanically
            locked breech using the short recoil method of operation. This rather conventional
            lock-up system has a large rectangular lug over the barrel's chamber that rides into
            and engages the ejection port cut-out in the slide. When a cartridge is fired,
            pressures generated by the ignited powder drive the cartridge casing back against the
            breech face on the slide, driving back both the barrel and slide as they remain
            locked together in the manner described above.
          \n
          \n %c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:
          \n %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] .45 Supressor.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp45_cw_match_descr">
        <text>
            The USP Match (9 mm Parabellum, .40 S&amp;W, .45 ACP) has the same features offered on
            the Expert, except for a barrel weight that replaces the elongated slide found on the
            Expert. This weight is said to provide a recoil counterbalance to aid in target
            tracking.It was discontinued in 1999. The USP was originally built around the .40 S&amp;W
            cartridge, but a 9×19mm Parabellum was introduced at the same time. In May 1995,
            Heckler &amp; Koch introduced a .45 ACP variant. The USP Compact series was introduced in
            1996 and is available in 9 mm Parabellum, .40 S&amp;W, .45 ACP, and, exclusively to the
            Compact model, .357 SIG. Other variants of the standard USP include the USP Tactical,
            USP Expert, USP Match, USP Elite and the standard sidearm of the German Armed Forces
            (Bundeswehr)—the P8. The USP Tactical .45 ACP variant is also in limited use by the
            Bundeswehr, designated as the P12.
          \n
          \n
        </text>
    </string>
</string_table>
